<videolist>

<item>
<title>Build Your World with Qt</title>
<thumbnail>Build_Your_World</thumbnail>
<link>Build_Your_World_With_Qt.mp4</link>
<description>Qt is the leading independent technology for cross-platform development. Create connected devices, UIs and applications that run anywhere on any device, on any operating system at any time.

Companies in over 70 industries use Qt to power millions of devices and applications. Build your world with Qt.
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bluescape</title>
<thumbnail>Bluescape</thumbnail>
<link>Bluescape_collaborative_workspace.mp4</link>
<description>Bluescape cloud-based visual collaborative workspace

With the support of Digia, Qt Services, Bluescape developed a special mapping software for teams to execute simultaneous collaboration on any device. Digia, Qt's knowledgeable team and performing technology resulted in Bluescape to look no further.
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Internet of Things</title>
<thumbnail>IoT</thumbnail>
<link>IoT_and_Qt.mp4</link>
<description>Internet of Things and Qt

The Qt Weather Station is a simple demo of how easy it is to create Internet of Things systems with Qt, the cross-platform application and UI framework.
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet Qt Creator</title>
<thumbnail>Meet_Qt_Creator</thumbnail>
<link>Meet_Qt_Creator.mp4</link>
<description>Cross-platform Integrated Development Environment

Whether you are creating a mobile app, desktop application or a connected embedded device, Qt Creator is the cross-platform IDE that makes application and UI development a breeze. Since time-to-market is key, the IDE includes productivity tools that speed up your development time.
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>3D Planets Example</title>
<thumbnail>3D_Planets</thumbnail>
<link>3D_Planets_Example.mp4</link>
<description>Qt 5.5 features the new Qt Canvas 3D module that lets you integrate 3D contents written with a WebGL-like API. the 3D Planets example is written with the Three.js 3D library. The same example is also implemented using the technology preview of the new Qt 3D module, using a Qt API.
</description>
</item>

</videolist>
